Yes, Sena-chan.
はい、せなちゃん
yes.
はい
I'm back at the hotel.
また来ましたね、ホテルに
You're here again.
また来ましたね
This time it's a bright spot.
今度は明るいところだよ
bright.
明るい
surely.
確かに
Isn't it a long time ago?
久々じゃない?
Hotel.
ホテル
Long time no see.
久々
It's been a long time.
めっちゃ久しぶり
It's already dark, it's dark,
もうさ、暗いところはさ、暗いところでさ、
It's kind of nice.
なんかいいじゃん
Bright places are bright places,
明るいところも明るいところでさ、
Isn't it good after all?
やっぱよくない?
It's embarrassing when it's bright.
明るいと恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I can still endure something.
まだなんか耐えれる
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
恥ずかしさある?
Is there one?
あるか
There is.
あるよ
Yes, there is.
あるよね
Hmmm.
うむです
Hmm?
うむ?
Yeah, I am.
うむですよ、私は
Do you have it?
持つんですか?
It's here again.
まただよ
I'm forced to do it.
やらされてます
Does it feel good?
いい感じ?
No, no, that's it.
いやいや、そんな
Always visual.
いつもビジュアルは
I don't like it.
嫌だな
How did you manage to do it?
何気にできたの?
Is it leaking?
漏れてる?
this.
これ
It's not leaking.
漏れてない
It opened and arrived.
開いてついた
It's quite different from before.
だいぶ違う、さっきと
Is it quite different?
だいぶ違う?
Is this one leaking?
こっちの方が漏れてる?
I don't know.
わかんない
Yeah, it's cute.
うん、かわいいよ
Sena-chan has a nice butt.
せなちゃんってさ、ね、お尻いいよね
Yes, that's often said.
はい、よく言われます
Is it often said?
よく言われる?
Your butt is really nice.
お尻やっぱいいよね
Let's enjoy butt play.
お 尻プレイ堪能しようかな
Today is that kind of day.
今日はそういう日だ
I guess I'll do that today.
今日はそういう日にしようかな
A day to enjoy ass play.
お尻プレイ堪能の日
Fairly good.
まあまあ、よい
good?
よい?
Isn't your butt really nice too?
お尻だってめちゃくちゃよくない?
Yes, I get compliments a lot.
うん、よく褒められる
This cute loli girl.
この、かわいいロリ系の落ちり
Isn't it the best?
最高じゃない?
What do you think?
どうなんでしょう?
Isn't it the best?
最高ですかね?
See that?
それさ、見えて?
I can't see it.
見えてないんですよ
Is that real?
それさ、本物?
Is it real?
本物か
picture?
え?
So, can you see it from here?
じゃ、こっからだってさ、 見えるんですか?
Um, what?
あの、なに?
There's something wrong with my pants these days.
なんかあれ、パンツあんじゃん、最近の
Wow, I can see it.
うわ、見えてんだ
I don't know if it's fake or not.
偽物なのか、偽物じゃないのか、わからん
Store bread is a fleeting color.
店パンは儚い色です
It's blue.
青だね
No, it's black.
じゃない、黒だよ
black?
黒?
Today I painted everything black.
今日は 全部黒にしました
Black coordinate?
ブラックコーデー?
yes.
はい
Well, please stand up.
じゃ、立ってみて
My coordination suddenly stops working.
急にコーデーションがやじまっちゃう
What do you think, okay?
どうでしょう、ちゃんと?
This kind of thing.
こういう系の
nice.
いいね
Does it feel good?
いい感じですか?
Yeah.
うん
What is that?
それ、なに?
Just try rolling it up.
ちょっと、ペロンって巻いてみて
This, ah, this?
これ、あ、これ?
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
Even though you say that, you always do it properly.
って言いながら、いつもちゃんとやってくれんじゃん
picture?
え?
Please do a little more perron.
もうちょっと、ペロンってやってよ
more?
もっと?
Yeah.
うん
It's tight, so everything goes up.
タイトだから、全部上がっちゃう
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
behind.
後ろ
Achachacha.
あちゃちゃちゃ
cute.
かわいい
Ahh, that's cute.
あ ちゃちゃ、かわいいね
One more time.
もう一回
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
Is it bad if it's close?
近いとダメなの?
It's close
近いな
ah.
ぁ
After all, your butt is beautiful.
や っぱ、お尻きれいだよね
It might be beautiful.
きれいかも
Be a mirror for a moment.
ちょっと、前鏡になって
yes.
そう
So, sit back a little.
で、ちょっと腰を落として
You're going to drop your foot.
足を落とすんだよね
There.
そ こ
Drop your feet, lower your hips.
足を落として、腰を落として
yes.
そう
Just like that, squeeze.
そのまま、ぎゅーって
picture?
え?
yes.
そう
Get on your knees and squeeze.
立ち膝になって、ぎゅーってやって
Yeah.
うん
Your butt is so beautiful.
お尻めっちゃきれい
Shake your ass.
ふりふりして、お尻
Get excited and shake it up.
ノリノリでふりふりしてよ
It's never happened.
あったことない
Now your asshole, Gambira.
今、お尻の穴、ガンビラ
Oh, please stop.
え、やめてください
Is it true?
はずい?
Twitching, butt hole.
ひくひくして、お尻の穴
Eh, how?
え、どうやって?
It becomes soft.
柔らかくなるんだ
yes.
そう
twitching
ひくひく
do.
して
It's here.
ここ だよ
Ah, yes.
ああ、そう
It's done, it's done.
できてる、できてる
Now, try twitching your pussy.
じゃ、マンコひくひくしてみて
Oh, that's it.
ああ、それは
Is it the same?
同じで?
It doesn't seem embarrassing at all.
まったく恥ずかしそうじゃないな
Something, something.
なんか もう、なんか
It doesn't seem embarrassing at all.
全然恥ずかしそうじゃない
That's not true.
そんなことはない
Remove the top and bottom.
上も下も抜く
Anyway, what do you mean by underwear?
とりあえず、 下着ってこと?
It becomes underwear.
下着になる
That's fine.
いいですよ
Can I take it off myself?
自分で脱いちゃっていい?
Do you want me to take it off?
脱がしてほしいの?
No, I'll take it off myself.
いや、自分で脱ぎますよ
No, I don't like it.
いや、嫌なんだ
No, I'll take it off myself.
いや、自分で脱ぎますよ
It's true, it's black.
ほんとだ、ブラックだね
It's black black.
ブラックブラックだね
I've never tried it before, so it might be a good idea.
今まで探証したこともないし、 いいかもしれない
Yes, mugyu.
はい、むぎゅーして
Mugyu.
むぎゅー
I can't.
できない
why?
なんで?
Huh, did your boobs get smaller?
え、おっぱい小さくなったの?
Hey, he's grown up.
ひゃん、大きくなったの
Sena-chan.
せなちゃん
Sena-chan, wasn't she an E cup?
せなちゃん、Eカップじゃなかったっけ?
It's gotten smaller.
小さくなったんですね
It's an E cup.
Eカップだよね
It was an E cup, right?
Eカップだったよね
But I feel like it's gotten smaller.
でもなんか、小さくなった気がします
Try mugging.
むぎゅーしてみて
Mugyu.
むぎゅー
Did it get smaller?
小さくなったの?
It's not getting smaller.
小さくなってないよ
perhaps.
たぶん
Will you call me?
呼びます?
Oh, that's how I feel.
え、そういう感想
I was looking for a little something, so the answer was a little different.
ちょっと求めていたから、 答えたらちょっと違う
When I arrived, I was told it was cold, but when I asked, it was cold.
ついたら寒いとか、 聞いたら冷まったんだけどね
Any other thoughts?
他の感想は?
Hmm.
うーん
It was kind of scary.
なんか、怖かった
The thrill.
スリルが
It was full of people.
人がいっぱいいたし
Maybe there was.
いたかも
Maybe you're being watched.
見られてるかも
That's what I thought when I thought about it.
って思ったらちょっとこう思いました
Maybe someone noticed.
たぶん、気づいてた人いたかもね
Hey, I definitely was.
ねえ、絶対いたよ
Absolutely.
絶対ね
We're having sex.
セックスしてるわ
Oh, it’s true!
あ、本当だ!
That's what he said.
とか言ってたし
I wonder what was true.
何が本当だったんだろうね
Hey, really.
ねえ、本当に
I wonder if you've heard the rumors.
噂でも聞いてたのかね
There are people who are doing it.
やってる人がいるよって
I was called quietly.
そ っと呼ばれてきた
Because this is a hotel.
これはホテルだから
Completely.
完全に
Because that's the kind of place it is.
そういう場所だからね
I'm keeping it separate here.
ここで別にしてるの
Hey, don't say anything.
ねえ、何も言わない
I'm calm.
落ち着いてる
When you're in charge of your butt.
お尻を担当すると
law.
ほう
It's like being in charge of the butt.
お尻担当みたいですね
It's amazing how different it is from the outside.
すごい外と違いがあいずいてる
It's such a relief.
すごいホッとするね
surely.
たしかに
There is also a sense of security.
安心感もある
I wonder if it can be done so calmly.
こんなに落ち着いてできるものなのかな
Well, it was nice to be outside.
まあ、外は外でよかったけどね
It looks like a cosplay character.
なんかコスプレキャラみたいだね
Looks like an anime character.
アニメキャラみたいだね
The blonde hair looks like it.
金髪がゆえにみたいな
If it's a little dark.
ちょっと暗かったら
Spread it out a little.
ちょっと広げて
Twitch.
ヒクヒクして
Is it done?
できてます?
It's done.
できてる
Hollow up.
くりむいて
Try peeling it off at the tip.
先ぐらいむいてみて
It hurts, right?
痛いでしょ
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
恥ずかしいよね
Too close.
近すぎて
I took pictures of embarrassing places.
恥ずかしいところ撮ってんだよ
About a while ago.
前ぐらい
what happened?
どうしたの?
The entrance chicken is amazing.
入り口チキンめっちゃ
Chicken at the entrance?
入り口チキンが?
What the heck is the entrance chicken?
入り口チキンがめっちゃ何なの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
what?
なに?
Are you back?
もどもどしてる?
Is it better around here?
この辺のほうがいいのかな?
Strong closure.
閉鎖強いな
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
嫌じゃないの
You can use it on the other side as well.
反対側も使えるからね
This one too?
こ っちも?
That's right.
そうだよ
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
Were you impressed?
感動した?
It's not just a handle.
ただの持ち手じゃないんだよ
This one too.
こっちも
It's a mask, right?
面でしょ
so...
そんなに...
This will fit in.
入るでしょこれ
I guess you can't come in.
入らないですかね
Huh?
あれ?
I guess this won't fit.
入らないのかなこれ
If this doesn't fit, is it a dick?
これ入らなかったらチンコ?
It won't come in, right?
入らないんじゃない?
I'm not going in.
入 っていかないよ
I can't get in.
入らない
Does that mean I can't have sex?
セックスできないってこと?
this.
これ
Ends today?
今日終了?
good.
いい
What?
え、なに?
Is it home?
家としいの?
Build a house too.
家も作って
Please be kind.
優しくしてください
That's why he's so mean.
それで意地悪していくんだよね
no.
いや
Relax.
力抜いてね
But I think I'll put it in.
でも入れそう
enter?
入る?
I entered.
入った
Did you come in for a while?
ちょっと入った?
Are you going to let me in?
中に入れんのか、じゃあ
It's just the dick.
チンコだけってことね
I laughed.
笑った
If you go in.
入っていけば
It's a mess.
めちゃくちゃじゃん
I agree.
そうだね
That's good.
上そうだね
sad.
悲しい
It's getting higher.
もっと高くなってきたね
bed.
ベッドを
The one you added to the bottom is in there.
一番奥まで加えておいた方が入ってる
Yeah.
うん
picture?
え?
Deepest?
一番奥?
Yeah.
うん
TRUE?
本当?
It's not even half full.
半分も入ってないよね
Get your hands dirty.
手しっちゃえの
yes.
そう
It seems like my dick will come in at any time,
チンコはいつでも入りさそうだけど、
I wonder if I should loosen up a few more pieces of Shasha.
もう ちょっとシャシャを何個ちょっとほぐしたほうがいいかな
Get your dick in.
チンコ入って
Shall we loosen up a little more?
もうちょっとほぐそうか
Do you want me to sleep?
寝 てもらう?
In your head?
頭で?
Yeah.
うん
Are you going to take pictures?
撮りすんの?
It's reflected, it's reflected.
映ってる映ってる
How about this?
これでどうかな?
Will you accept it?
受け付けてくれるかな?
Like I said earlier, not at all.
さっきのほら、 全然
I couldn't get in.
入らなかった
Because they didn't accept me in the middle,
真ん中受け付けてくれなかったからさ、
The tea from earlier.
さっきのお茶さ
What if it was this?
これだったらどうかなって
What is that?
何それ?
Okay, look.
いいよ、見て
Ah, I think this will fit.
あ、これ入りそうだ
I'm in. I'm in.
入った入った
It has a router in it.
スルータ入ってんだ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Understood.
わかった
Well, here's your head too.
じゃあ頭こっちも
Shall I do it?
手しちゃう?
Yeah.
うん
Okay, head.
いいよ、頭
You can leave the head as is.
頭、そのまま付けていいよ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
Excuse me, just a little longer.
もうちょっと、すみません、もう
mango.
マ ンゴー
Look.
ほら
This is crazy.
やばこれ
This is embarrassing so I thought I'd do it this way.
これ恥ずかしいからこうさせてやろうと思って
What is this?
何これ?
Kuruni?
くるに?
Successfully repeat.
うまくり返し
I can't help it?
しょうがない?
I don't know.
知らん
Can't you see your mango?
自分のマンゴー見えてないの?
Yeah.
うん
I can't see it.
見えないんだ
It's the angle where you can't see it.
ミソで見えない角度なんだね
I like the body.
体カッパいいね
Yes, but this got me interested.
そう、でもこれで気になったから
What an embarrassing angle.
てか何恥ずかしい角度だね
Then I'll put my dick in.
じゃあチンコ入れちゃう
A dick is better than a finger or a toy, right?
指よりもおもちゃよりもチンコはいいんでしょ?
Yeah, my favorite.
うん、一番好き
It immediately gives off the feeling that it's not like that.
なんかそれじゃない感すぐ出しちゃうね
Toys, fingers, etc.
おもちゃとか指とかさ
Isn't that true?
そんなことない?
real?
ほんと?
I understand quite a bit.
結構分かったよな
Hurry up and put your dick in.
早くチンコ入れてって
Mango is hot.
マンゴーなんか暑い
hot?
暑い?
Yeah.
うん
Can it be turned upside down?
ひっくり立てられる?
Looks like it's hot.
暑いだそう
Can you move up and down slowly?
ゆっくりゆっくり上下できる?
Oh, you can go up and down.
ああ、上下できるね
slowly.
ゆっくり
Is this easier?
こっちの方が楽?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Show me your ass that never disappears.
消えないお尻を見せて
Let me say it myself.
自分で言ってもらおう
A little burst of laughter
ちょっと爆笑
mosquito.
か
yes.
そう
I agree.
そう ですね
How long was it intense?
いつまで激しかった?
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Yeah.
うん
Don't you like intense competition?
激しいせっかくが嫌いなの?
Yeah.
うん
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
The blonde Sena-chan is also nice.
金髪のセナちゃんもいいね
It's the first and the last.
最初で最後です
First and last?
最初で最後?
First and last.
最初で最後
I even cum inside her.
中出しもしたしさ
I have nothing to say.
何も言うことない
Just give me a cleaning blowjob at the end.
最後お掃除フェラーだけして
yes.
はい
I'm not feeling any better, I'm sensitive.
少しくしてないよ、敏感だわ